It was rather interesting just to watch them gathering
their materials and bouncing around their, what they call it,
kangaroo walk or something like that.
Who named it that?
I don't know.
I bet those men are going to get quite a reception when
they get back to Maine.
Oh, yes.
I'll be so glad when they land back now.
But I think that's pretty well a fact,
because they've landed so many safely now.
but I feel relieved. Just getting off of the moon was the thing that was...
Have they met with the one that was circling?
Yes, they've rendezvoused. So I understand. That wasn't shown either, so I...
But they say they have rendezvoused, so that's a matter of making the circles and then coming down.
What do you sort of imagine for the future? Do you imagine them sending a ship?
I think they will. I think they will.
And we'll do some more exploring up there.
Very positive, they left us a hand with that.
Because that was such a very small area,
when you think of it, that they just gathered rocks and, oh,
samples of soil and all.
And they did a probe for some samples.
And just what was going to come of that, I don't know.
I'd be glad to read it.